benq.com 2013-11-19

# Legal Notice | BenQ Global

##  Your Privacy

At BenQ website, we believe you have a right to know what type of information we may collect when you interact with us and our practices with respect to that information. The guidelines contained herein apply only to the BenQ websites. Sites which are linked to/from BenQ websites and via banner ads may have different policies; therefore, please review the privacy policy notices on those sites for details. In order to participate in BenQ websites, it will be necessary for you to provide certain personally identifiable information, including your name, e-mail address, age, mailing address, city, state and zip code and BenQ websites username and password. If you choose not to provide this information, you will not be able to participate in BenQ websites.

##  Collection of Information:

For each visitor to the BenQ website, BenQ' web server automatically recognizes, collects and/or stores information such as the visitor's IP address/Domain name combination and any referring sites. BenQ may use several technologies to accomplish this. Examples of such technologies are cookies and web beacons. When you visit BenQ' websites or advertisements appearing thereon, or use one or more of the BenQ website services, or receive e-mails from BenQ we may use an industry-wide technology called "cookies" which stores certain information on your computer and which will allow us to customize your experience to better match your interests and preferences or to simply facilitate your signing in to use the services. Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However, if you block or erase cookies, we may not be able to restore any preferences or customization settings you previously specified and our ability to personalize your online experience would be limited. Please refer to your browser instructions or "help" screen to learn more about these functions. BenQ may also itself use, or engage third parties to use, Web beacons for researching certain usage and activities on our Website. The information collected by BenQ or requested from third parties through these Web beacons is in an aggregate, non-individually identifiable form and is used to find out more about users including demographic information and usage patterns for more accurate reporting and to improve the effectiveness of our marketing. BenQ may also itself use, or engage third parties to use, pixel tags or other technology to research or track your usage activities with respect to e-mails from us. BenQ may ask you to provide "personal information", meaning individually identifiable information such as your e-mail address, name, mailing address, telephone number, social security number, credit card number, or persistent identifier (such as a customer number held in a cookie) which is associated with individually identifiable information, to enable you to participate in contests, on bulletin boards, to fill out a registration, or to order products and services using these sites. BenQ may combine the information you provide on our Websites with information we may collect offline from you or from third parties so that we can more effectively tailor our site, services and offerings to you.

**_BenQ will not share the personal information you provide with any other parties, except_** (a) to other affiliated BenQ companies (i.e., (i) BenQ Corporation, (ii) any company of which 50% or more of its outstanding shares are owned by BenQ Corporation, directly or indirectly, and (iii) any company with the name "BENQ" as a part of its trade name) who may want to contact you about products, services or other offerings that may be of interest to you (BenQ and such affiliates being collectively referred to as "BenQ"), (b) with your consent (see paragraph below), (c) as may be required by law or court order, (d) to persons or companies with whom BenQ engages to carry out or provide support for the operations of the sites or our business, or (e) to appropriate third parties, including law enforcement or other government agencies, in connection with a criminal investigation, fraud prevention, or other legal action or if BenQ reasonably believes it is necessary to do so to protect BenQ, its customers, or the public.

**_Unless you instruct us otherwise,_** BenQ may contact you to provide information about products, services, promotions, contests, or other activities or offerings that may be of interest to you. You can instruct us as to your contact preferences by checking or un-checking the box indicating your preference, as applicable, at the time you register to join BenQ and thereafter by visiting the Your Profile web page, accessing the Messaging Tab and checking or un-checking the box indicating your preference, as applicable. In addition, with each communication you receive from BenQ, you will be given the opportunity to indicate if you do not wish to receive future communications from BenQ.

**_With your consent,_** BenQ may share your personal information with third parties outside of the BenQ group of companies who may want to contact you about products, services or other offerings that may be of interest to you. Each of these companies may have their own privacy policies. BenQ will seek to obtain your consent at the time you register to join BenQ either by an "opt-out" or "opt-in" method, or by other means (such as an e-mail request). If you consent to receiving communications from any of these third parties, you will need to communicate with them directly if you later decide that you no longer wish to receive their communications. If you wish to withdraw your consent from any further sharing of your personal information with third parties, you may do so by visiting the Your Profile web page, accessing the Messaging Tab and checking or un-checking the box indicating your preference, as applicable.

**To change or update the personal information you have provided to BenQ,** please visit Your Profile web page and click on the appropriate tab for the information you wish to revise or update.

##  Use and Disclosure of Anonymous Aggregated Information

BenQ may also collect, aggregate and maintain anonymous information about you, such as your hobbies, interests, purchasing habits, music preferences, and the like. This data can then be used to tailor BenQ Reward's promotions, advertising, and communications to deliver a better experience for you. BenQ may also share such aggregate information with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties; for example, to inform them about the percentage of male/female visitors to our site or the percentage of visitors within a particular age range.

##  Security

BenQ takes great care in maintaining the security of your personal information and in preventing unauthorized access to it through the use of appropriate technology and internal procedures. However, BenQ does not guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur.

Notice To/Regarding Children Under the Age of 13

BenQ is open only to individuals who are 13 years of age and older. If you are under 13 years of age, any information you submit will not be retained by BenQ.

BenQ believes that children using the Internet require special protection, and we urge parents or guardians to explain Internet safety to their children. Parents are urged to spend time online with their children to become familiar with the types of content available on the Internet. Control tools are available from online services and software manufacturers to help create a safer environment for children.

##  Consent to Processing:

By providing any personal information to BenQ, all persons, including without limitation persons in the member states of the European Union, fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in the United States of America.

##  Policy Governs Use: Changes to Privacy Policy

The terms of this policy will govern the use and any information collected while it is in place. BenQ reserves the right to change this policy at any time, so please re-visit this page as often as you wish. In case of any material change, we will change the "Last Update" date in this privacy policy and/or post a notice on the site. Changes to this privacy policy are effective as of the stated "Last Update" date and your continued use BenQ on or after the "Last Update" date will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes.

##  Notice to California Residents - Your California Privacy Rights:

If you are a California resident, you have the right to receive: a) information identifying any third party company(ies) to whom BenQ may have disclosed, within the past year, personal information pertaining to you and your family for that company's direct marketing purposes; and b) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. To obtain such information, please e-mail your request via the Contact link of BenQ website.

##  Questions:

If you have any questions or comments about our personal information practices or about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to write us at:

BenQ Corporation

16 Jihu Road

Neihu, Taipei

TAIWAN
